childrensalonoutlet.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy policy | Childrensalon Outlet

We will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:

  * Where we need to fulfil a sales contract (your order) we have entered into with you.
  * Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.
  * Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.

Generally we do not rely on consent as a legal basis for processing your personal data other than in relation to sending third party direct marketing communications to you via email or text message. You have the right to withdraw consent to marketing at any time by contacting us.

Purposes for which we will use your personal data

We have set out below, in a table format, a description of all the ways we plan to use your personal data, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate.

Note that we may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. Please contact us if you need details about the specific legal ground we are relying on to process your personal data where more than one ground has been set out in the table below.

**Purpose/Activity**

| 

**Type of data**

| 

**Lawful basis for processing including basis of legitimate interest**  
  
---|---|---  
  
To register you as a new customer

| 

  1. Identity
  2. Contact

| 

Performance of a contract with you  
  
To process and deliver your order including:

  1. Manage payments, fees and charges
  2. Collect and recover money owed to us

| 

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Financial
  4. Transaction
  5. Marketing and Communications

| 

  1. Performance of a contract with you
  2. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to recover debts due to us)

To manage our relationship with you which will include:

  1. Notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy
  2. Asking you to leave a review or take a survey

| 

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Profile
  4. Marketing and Communications

| 

  1. Performance of a contract with you
  2. Necessary to comply with a legal obligation
  3. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study how customers use our products/services)

To enable you to partake in a prize draw, competition or complete a survey

| 

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Profile
  4. Usage
  5. Marketing and Communications

| 

  1. Performance of a contract with you
  2. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them and grow our business)

To administer and protect our business and this website (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data)

| 

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Technical

| 

  1. Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise)
  2. Necessary to comply with a legal obligation

To deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you

| 

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Profile
  4. Usage
  5. Marketing and Communications
  6. Technical

| 

Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to inform our marketing strategy)  
  
To use data analytics to improve our website, products/services, marketing, customer relationships and experiences

| 

  1. Technical
  2. Usage

| 

Necessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our website updated and relevant, to develop our business and to inform our marketing strategy)  
  
To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may be of interest to you

| 

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Technical
  4. Usage
  5. Profile

| 

Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business)  
  
Marketing

We strive to provide you with choices regarding certain personal data uses, particularly around marketing and advertising. You can view and make certain decisions about your personal data use in the “my account” section of the website, or by contacting us.

Promotional offers from us

We may use your Identity, Contact, Technical, Usage and Profile Data to form a view on what we think you may want or need, or what may be of interest to you. This is how we decide which products, services and offers may be relevant for you.

You will receive marketing communications from us if you have requested information from us or purchased [goods or services] from us or if you provided us with your details when you entered a competition or registered for a promotion and in each case you have consented to our communicating with you for these purposes.

Third-party marketing

We will get your express opt-in consent before we share your personal data with any company outside the Childrensalon group of companies for marketing purposes.

Opting out

You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by logging into the website and checking or unchecking relevant boxes to adjust your marketing preferences or by following the opt-out/unsubscribe links on any electronic marketing message sent to you or by [contacting us at any time].

Where you opt out of receiving these marketing messages, this will not apply to personal data provided to us as a result of [a product/service purchase, warranty registration, product/service experience or other transactions].

Cookies

In order to collect the anonymous data described in the preceding paragraph, we may use cookie technology on our website.

A cookie is a small piece of information which is sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive, mobile phone or other device. Cookies do not damage your computer.

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. This enables you to decide if you want to accept it or not. However, some of the services and features offered through our website may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

We use two types of cookies on our website:

Strictly necessary cookies

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features. Without these cookies, services you have asked for cannot be provided. They are deleted when you close the browser.

Performance cookies

These cookies collect information in an anonymous form about how visitors use our website.

They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around the site when they are using it.

We may also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our website and to improve the service we offer to you. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your computer on a network, or in this case, the internet. Your IP address might also be used to gather broad demographic information.

We may perform IP lookups to determine which domain you are coming from (ie aol.com, yourcompany.com) to more accurately gauge our users' demographics.

Information from these types of cookies and technologies or about website usage is not combined with information about you from any other source.

None of the cookies or technologies that we use will personally identify you.

Change of purpose

We will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to get an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us.

If we need to use your personal data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.

Please note that we may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.
